

Wilson Dlamini

27 Bond Street, Clydesdale Pretoria - 0002 Gauteng, South AFrica E-mail: wilzmar.kwd@gmail.com

Phone: (061) 482 4765

OBJECTIVE

Outgoing waiter/bartender with +3 years experience in hospitality and customer service seeking a position as a sales consultant where extensive experience will be further developed and utilized. Competitiveness and efficiency are one my key goals for obtaining the best results. I have the intelligence, determination, stork market knowledge and professional expertise to grow in the new role in marketing your company.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Crawdaddy's

November 2018 — Present

Waiter

- Welcome and sit customers.
- Up-sell food and drinks.
- Maintain good service and presentation.

CasaBella

April 2018 — October 2018

Waiter

- Welcome and sit customers.
- Up-sell food and drinks.
- Maintain good service and presentation.

Amilak Marketing

April 2018 — May 2018

Sales and Marketing

- Field training on selling Financial services.
- Extensive training on fundamentals of sales like the law of average, 5-steps, 8-steps and impulse factors in effective communication.
- Keys objectives in authenticity, fraudulent behavior and related laws.
- Maintaining short-term and long-term goals in sale turnout.
- Introduction to leadership skills and project management

Koi

September 2015 — April 2015

Waiter

- Welcome and sit customers.
- Up-sell food and drinks.
- Maintain good service and presentation.

News Cafe Menlyn

December 2014 — August 2015

Bartender

- Stock counting
- Bar service
- Cash bar management

Wilson Dlamini

QUALIFICATIONS

- Certified Pastel Intermediate
- Bcom (Informatics) Incomplete
- Front-End Development web applications

EDUCATION

Bcom (Informatics)

February 2012 — November 2014

University of Pretoria

Majors: C# programming, Accounting, Statistics, Economics, Business Management, communications management, Discrete structures, Informatics.

Web Development

April 2018 — Present

 ${\sf FreeCodeCamp}$

HTML, CSS, JavaScript

INTERESTS

Learning, Entrepreneurship, Travel, Music, Movies

REFERENCES

Other documents will be available upon request.

Wilson Dlamini